PRIVACY POLICY PARKINGCREW
--------------------------

Thank you for visiting this domain/website. The website provider takes the protection of your personal data very seriously. This Privacy Policy informs you about the collection and processing of personal data on this website. Personal data collected on this website is always treated in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations, including, but not limited, the regulations of the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

1\. WEBSITE PROVIDER AND CONTROLLER
-----------------------------------

The website provider and controller (according to Art. 4 (7) GDPR) can be contacted via the contact data provided in the imprint or via the contact form on this website.

2\. DATA PROCESSOR (ADVERTISING TECHNOLOGY PLATFORM)
----------------------------------------------------

The advertising content of this website is provided via the advertising technology platform of Team Internet AG, Liebherrstr. 22, 80538 Munich, Germany.

Please note that Team Internet AG provides the technical infrastructure for the monetization of this domain via the advertising technology platform of Team Internet AG only.

Team Internet AG is not the domain owner and controller, and Team Internet AG is not responsible for the content of this website and the data processing in the context of the provisioning of this website.

For any questions or concerns regarding data protection on this website, please contact the website provider and controller. Alternatively, you can also contact the data protection officer of Team Internet AG, Rechtsanwalt Christian Schmoll, via email at [privacy@teaminternet.com](mailto:privacy@teaminternet.com).

3\. VISITING THIS WEBSITE
-------------------------

### 3.1 Log Files

Each time you visit this website, data and information from the computer system of the calling computer is collected. The following data is logged:

* IP address of the calling computer
* Operating system of the calling computer
* Browser version of the calling computer
* Name of the retrieved file/website
* Date and time of retrieval
* Transferred amount of data
* Referring URL

This data is processed in order to be able to provide the website, to ensure the security, availability and integrity of the website (e.g., detection and defense against DoS attacks or access by bots), to improve the quality and presentation of the website, to be able to identify and correct errors and for statistical purposes. This data is automatically deleted after seven days.

The legal basis for this data processing is the website providers legitimate interest in the abovementioned purposes pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR.

### 3.2 Content Delivery Network

This website uses content delivery networks (CDN) to increase the security and delivery speed of the website. A content delivery network is a network of servers distributed worldwide that is capable of delivering optimized content to users. For this purpose, personal data, including your IP address, may be processed by the provider of the content delivery networks. The providers of the content delivers networks act as data processors for the website provider.

Since a CDN represents a network of servers distributed worldwide, the use of a CDN may result in the transfer of personal data to a third country without an adequate level of data protection. In this case, it is ensured that appropriate safeguards are provided for the transfer in accordance with Art. 46 GDPR.

The legal basis for this data processing is the website providers legitimate interest in increasing the security and the delivery speed of the website pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR.

### 3.3 Unique View ID

For the provision of our service, to continuously improve the website and our services and for fraud prevention, we create a Unique View ID. The data thus collected is stored on our servers in such a way that you as a user remain anonymous to us.

In doing so, we collect the following data:

* Abbreviated/anonymized IP address of the user's calling system

Your full IP address is deleted immediately in the course of anonymization.

The legal basis for this data processing is our legitimate interest pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f) DSGVO. Our overriding legitimate interest are the above-mentioned purposes.

4\. CONTACT
-----------

If you contact the domain owner via a contact form on the website, the domain owner will process your data to process your request. The contact form is provided by Team Internet AG as a data processor pursuant to Art. 28 GDPR.

The integration and use of the contract form may involve the transfer of personal data to a third country without an adequate level of data protection. In this case, it is ensured that appropriate safeguards are provided for the transfer in accordance with Art. 46 GDPR.

The legal basis for this data processing is the website providers legitimate interest in the communication with website visitors pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR and, if applicable, the selling of the domain pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. b) GDPR.

5\. ADSENSE FOR DOMAINS
-----------------------

This website may use Google AdSense for Domains. Google AdSense for Domains is an online service that enables the provisioning of the advertising content of this website. Google AdSense for Domains is provided by Google Ireland Limited in Ireland ("Google").

When you visit this website, a request is sent to Google and Google processes the domain name and the IP address of the website visitor to dynamically return the advertising content of the website. Google AdSense for Domains sets a cookie. The display of the advertising content is the primary purpose of this website, and the setting of the cookie is technically necessary to provide the advertising content of the website.

The advertising content is not personalized, and no profile of the website visitor is generated.

You can prevent the setting of cookies by Google AdSense for Domains by setting your browser accordingly, in particular by suppressing cookies from third-party providers, and thus prevent cookies from being set.

Further information about the purpose and scope of the data processing in the context of Google AdSense for Domains is provided here: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

The use of Google AdSense for Domains may involve the transfer of personal data to a third country without an adequate level of data protection. In this case, it is ensured that appropriate safeguards are provided for the transfer in accordance with Art. 46 GDPR.

The legal basis for this data processing is the website providers legitimate interest in the provisioning of the advertising content of the website and the monetization of the domain pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR.

6\. AGE RESTRICTION
-------------------

This website is not intended or designed for use by children under the age of 16. The website provider does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from or about anyone under the age of 16.

7\. RECIPIENTS OF DATA
----------------------

Personal data will only be passed on to third parties within the framework of legal requirements. Personal data will only be transferred to third parties if, for example, this is necessary for contractual purposes on the basis of Art. 6 (1) lit. b) GDPR or to safeguard the website provider�s overriding legitimate interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR in the effective conduct of specific business operations.

Insofar as service providers are used within the context of the provision of the website, appropriate legal precautions are taken as well as appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure the protection of your personal data.

8\. YOUR RIGHTS
---------------

You have the rights explained below with regard to the personal data processed by us concerning you:

### 8.1 Right of Access

You can request information in accordance with Art. 15 GDPR about your personal data that is processes by the website provider.

### 8.2 Right to Rectification

If the information concerning you is not (or no longer) accurate, you may request a correction in accordance with Art. 16 GDPR. If your data is incomplete, you may request that the data is completed.

### 8.3 Right to Erasure

You may request the erasure of your personal data in accordance with Art. 17 GDPR.

### 8.4 Right to Restriction of Processing

In accordance with Art. 18 GDPR you have the right to request restriction of processing of your personal data.

### 8.5 Right to Object to Processing

You have the right to object at any time on grounds relating to your particular situation to the processing of your personal data which is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 (1) lit. e) or lit. f) GDPR in accordance with Art. 21 (1) GDPR. In this case, the website provider will not further process your data unless compelling legitimate grounds for the processing can be demonstrated which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or if the processing serves to assert and exercise or defend against legal claims (Art. 21 (1) GDPR).

In addition, according to Art. 21 (2) DSGVO, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of personal data concerning you for the purposes of direct marketing; this also applies to any profiling, insofar as it is related to such direct marketing.

### 8.6 Right to Withdraw Consent

Insofar as you have given your consent for processing, you have a right to withdraw your consent pursuant to Art. 7 (3) GDPR.

### 8.7 Right to Data Portability

You have the right to receive the personal data concerning you collected in the context of your visit of the website in a structured, common and machine-readable format ("data portability") as well as the right to have this data transferred to another controller if the conditions of Art. 20 (1) lit. (a) and (b) GDPR are met.

### 8.8 Exercise of Rights

You can exercise your rights by notifying the website provider.

### 8.9 Right to complain to the Data Protection Authorities

If you believe that the processing of your personal data violates data protection law, you also have the right to complain to a data protection supervisory authority of your choice pursuant to Article 77 GDPR.

9\. COMPULSORY DATA AND PROFILING
---------------------------------

The provision of personal data is neither required by law nor by contract, and you are not obliged to provide personal data.

Automated decision making, including profiling, is not performed.

10\. INFORMATION SECURITY AND RETENTION
---------------------------------------

Appropriate technical and organizational measures are taken in accordance with the state of the art to ensure a level of protection for the personal data processed that is appropriate to the risk of the respective processing and to protect the data processed against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction or against access by unauthorized persons. A restrictive rights and roles concept on a "need to know" basis ensures that employees only have access to the personal data they absolutely need to perform their duties.

The principles of data avoidance and data economy are strictly adhered to and personal data is only stored for as long as is necessary to achieve the respective purpose of the data processing purposes or as stipulated by the storage periods provided by law. If the purpose of storage no longer applies or if a storage period provided for by law expires, the personal data will be routinely anonymized or deleted in accordance with the statutory provisions.

11\. AMENDMENT OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY
-------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time so that it always complies with current legal requirements or in order to implement technical changes to the website and/or additional services implemented on the website.
